《死神来了3》
恶魔
Devil
你相信命运吗？
Do you believe in fortunes?
幸运
Luck
命运
Fate
死亡
Death
哇！
Aah!
耶…哈哈！
Oh, man! Heh heh.
- 看到没有？- 喔！
- Did you see that? - Woo!
我的天 哈哈！
Oh, my God. Ha ha!
- 耶！- 真棒！
- Yes! Yes! - Nice, nice, nice.
- 真要命！- 没白来
- Aw, sick! - Worth the wait.
哦 宝贝 你错过机会了
Oh, babe. You missed out.
耶！
Yes!
我要下去！
I want to get off.
高空死亡
HIGH DIE
真是够刺激！
That was intense, man.
体验一回「粉身碎骨」的感觉
To feel how that would be to just crash and burn like that.
是啊 也许你感觉不错吧 我们魂都吓掉了
Yeah, yeah. Maybe for you, but our lives are actually goin' somewhere.
好了 下一个目标 云霄飞车
Oh! OK, well, where we gotta go is to the roller coaster.
我们的通行证只到9：15
'Cause our pass is for 9:15.
错过这次 就得再排上…
If we miss that, we'll stand in line…
差不多一天半的队 那可得要我的命
for, like, a day and a half, and that's gonna kill me.
- 好吧 - 准备好了？
- OK! - All right?
走吧
So let's go.
麦金利高中 05级 毕业晚会
Welcome mc klnley hlgh grad party 05
他们全准备消遣这家伙！
They're totally gonna dig this man!
行了 先去吃点炸薯喝杯可乐不碍事吧
OK. Come on, it won't kill us to get a deep-fried Snickers and a Coke.
坐恶魔航班之前？那会杀了我
Before ridin' Devil's Flight? Yeah, that might kill me.
不 未能击垮你的事会使你变得更强
No! What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, man.
- 哇！- 哈哈
- Unh! - Ha ha!
哦 这个我来拿
Oh, I'll take that.
少来了 还我…相机不是我的
No. Come on, gimme. It's not even mine, Kevin.
是借来拍同学录的 凯文…给我
It's the yearbook's. Just…Kevin.
哈哈！
Ha ha!
- 噢！- 拍到了！
- Oh! - Oh, got it.
- 老天！你真是个白痴 - 嗨！给我…
- Oh, my God, you're such an idiot. - Hey. Hey. Gimme the…
哈！
Ha ha!
- 喔！- 干得好！
- Ow! - Nice.
呃…你能不能把刚才史黛西那张删了？
Um, could you, like, please delete that one of Stacy?
这些照片是拍来制作同学录的
These are for the yearbook.
明天就是最后期限 我得赶着交过去
And I have to turn them in tomorrow to make a deadline…
至于小林 史黛西的裙下春光能否入选
and, like, I doubt it if a shot of Stacy Kobayashi's camel toe…
我就不知道了
is gonna make it in there.
真要有了 我买两份
Whew. l'd buy two.
哈哈！
Ha ha ha!
38号 你们点的东西好了
Number 38, your order's ready.
是我们的
That's us.
真不好意思
I am so sorry.
凯文总是玩过界
Kevin can get so out of control.
他总是把我逼到崩溃边缘
Let me just say he would make me crazy.
我是说…你晓得我是个控制狂
Ha! I mean, you know I'm such a control freak…
可我却控制不了他
like I couldn't handle that.
我要和他分手
I'm breaking up with him.
毕业以后几周之内就提出来
Couple of weeks. After graduation.
这主意不是一时冲动
I've been wanting to for a while.
不过别告诉别人啊
But don't tell anybody, OK?
喔…
Whoa. Ha ha!
给那边来一张 到时候同学录绝对大卖
Now, that shot there? That'll sell some yearbooks.
- 我喜欢 - 我也是
- I love it. - I love it.
好吧 谁叫我这么爱控制
Oh! Oh, all right, so I'm a total whore.
加油！加油！
Come on, go, go, go, go, go, go go!
天啊 阿什丽 你就要赢了！
Oh, my God, Ashley, you're winning. You're totally winning.
- 是吗？- 再加把劲 快！
- Am I winning? - Yeah, come on, hurry!
加油！加油！
OK, come on, come on, come on, come on!
我赢了？看看旁边的对手 我不想看
Am I winning? Look around, I don't want to look.
你赢定了！
You're totally winning.
加油！
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
- 别往旁边看 - 天啊！再加把劲！
- Don't look! - Oh, my God! Come on!
啊！我赢了！
Oh, my God! I'm winning! I'm winning!
啊！
Aah! Aah!
- 赢了！- 我说嘛
- I won! - I knew you would.
天啊 快把奖品给我！
Oh, my God! Gimme my prize.
- 祝贺你 - 真是太棒了 阿什丽
- Good job. - That was so awesome, Ashley.
阿什丽
Ashley.
喔！
Woo! Ha ha!
这位兄台 玩得尽兴吗？
How ya doin', my brother? You havin' a good time, huh?
- 你喜欢这个？- 哈！
- You like that? - Ha ha!
棒极了！来…
Yeah! You like it. Give it up. Give it up.
喔
Whoo-ooh!
山姆
Sam!
抱歉 你…
Excuse me.
你还没毕业吧
You're not a senior.
你要怎么办？
And what are you gonna do about it…
「甜心」小姐
Miss "Cutest Couple, " Rah Rah? Ha ha!
给妈讲了没？
Mom know you're here?
你要是去告状 就是彻底的小贱货
You are a complete bitch if you tell her.
有这可以作证
Proof where you were.
有种就拍这个
Take a shot of this.
哈！
Ha ha ha!
好 我就说嘛 是3
Yeah! That's what I'm talking about. That's three.
3 是3号
? That is three, number three?
我真有种
? Oh, I'm the man, I'm the man? Man, I am hot.
- 给我你们的手 - 这儿 这儿
- Man, gimme some right here, man. - Right here! Right here!
你在干嘛？滚远点
What you doin'? Get the fuck back. Hoo!
我真是了不起 再来一次
My God, I am good. Here we go.
伙计 让我告诉你什么是 见你的鬼…
Boy, I'll tell ya… Goddamn. Whoo!
轻点 先生 请站上去
Kind sir, step right up!
开始吧 想要什么？
There ya go. Whaddaya want?
来吧 宝贝 第3层 你们都是我的
Here we go, baby. 3 for 3. It's all mine.
来 来
Here we go. Here we go.
我要大奖 看好了
Big prize. Watch out. Come on.
是不是要这个 蓝色的吗？
We gonna get that one. You want that blue one?
我要这个
That's the one we gonna get.
你…跑不掉的
You can run, but you cannot hide.
- 耶 - 哇 就是这了
- Yes! - Whoo! Here we are, baby.
- 耶！- 喔！
- Yes! - Whoo!
- 就是它 - 酷毙了
- There it is. - Awesome.
来 拍张这个！
Here, get a pic of this. Ahhh!
这是一条不归路
This is the beginning of the end.
各位 排好队
Hey, guys, get in line.
再玩一次吧！
Let's go on again!
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我…
I'm…
我有种预感 就像…
I was having that feeling like deja vu, you know?
能看到还没有发生的事情
Except for something that hasn't happened yet.
杰！
Hey, J.
好了 快走吧
Come on, man, let's go.
- 好了 等一下 - 快点
- Yeah, yeah, hold on. - Come on.
怎么了？怕坐这个？
What, are you weirded out by the ride?
我了解你 我想是不是
'Cause, look, I know you. And I think that maybe…
你怕坐云霄飞车…
you're nervous about this roller coaster…
是因为他们说真正的恐怖…
because they say the real fear with these rides…
让你有种无法控制它的感觉
comes from the feeling of having no control.
人害怕时就会胡思乱想
Everyone imagines weird stuff when they get scared.
到头来现实绝不是想象那么糟
But it never turns out to be what they imagine.
永远都不是
Never.
好吧
OK.
你…逃不掉了
You can run, but you cannot hide.
啊 站在这里 要是你们把手抬起来
Oh! Where you guys are right now if you raise your hands and just…
做出「捧」的动作
Ha…cup them slightly…
看上去就像是 你们捧着那魔鬼的「蛋」
it'll look you're holding the devil's balls.
我们为什么要那样做？
And we'd wanna do that why?
到哪儿去找那么粗的「大棒」？
When else you ever gonna see a dick that big?
我眼前就有
I'm lookin' at one right now.
哈哈！你们俩真是够惹火！
Ha ha! Man, you guys are smokin' hot.
- 快滚开 弗兰基 - 你来这儿干吗？
- Get out, Frankie. - Yeah, why are you even here?
你都毕业两年了
Yeah, you graduated, like, two years ago.
我来关怀学妹的成长
I stuck around to monitor your development.
好了 可以走了
Yeah. Good to go. Good to go, baby.
来吧 来吧
Let's do it. Let's do it. Come on. Come on.
「恶魔航班」就是你的黄泉路
You may never return from Devil's Flight.
哈哈哈…
Ha ha ha ha!
弗兰基 别拍了
frankie, stop!
可别叫出声来哦
Try not to scream!
过了这门就没有出路了 我等着你 哈哈哈
Ha ha ha!
真是酷毙了！
That was totally awesome!
可不是
Yeah! Sweet!
你没事吧？
You all right?
没什么好担心的
There's nothing to worry about.
云霄飞车不过是 最简单的物理现象
A roller coaster is just elemental physics.
势能到动能的转换
A conversion of potential energy to kinetic energy.
是啊 死于云霄飞车事故的概率…
Yeah. Odds are like one in 250 million…
差不多是2500万分之一
of dying in a roller coaster.
多谢「提醒」 麦金利
Yeah, yeah, thanks for that, McKinley.
是的 开车去游乐园的路上出车祸…
You're more likely to die driving to an amusement park…
的概率都要高些
than dying at one.
终于到了
Here we go.
喔！
Whoo!
喜欢这个么？
You like this?
在滑滑梯比赛上赢的
Won it on the Wacky Ladder.
知道吗 那梯子真的很陡
You know that ladder deal that wobbles? Took it.
我很喜欢 是电影<母校>里的
I like this. It's old school.
弗兰基·齐克斯是母校校友 女士们
Frankie Cheeks is old school, ladies.
那是什么？哦 我很荣幸
What's that? Oh, well, it'd be my honor.
恶心
Ew.
我们走
Oh! Let's go.
嗨…宝贝
Hey…Baby.
- 几位？- 4位
- How many? - Uh, 4.
- 4位 - 恩
- 4. - Yeah.
呃…1号门
Uh, gate one.
- 耶 头座 - 真好！
- Yeah. Front car. - Yes!
等等…拜托
Wait…No. No, please.
别跟我争 我不想坐前面
I'm sorry, I don't wanna be a hassle. I just…I can't sit in the front.
我不想看到轨道 不然会抓狂的
I cannot see the tracks. I'll freak.
好吧 没关系
OK. Take it easy.
这个…凯丽会坐后面陪你
Uh, well, Carrie will sit in the back with you. Right, babe?
为什么是我？因为我是女的？
Uh! Why me? What? 'Cause we're girls?
去他妈的 我就要去伯克利了 有段时间玩不成这个
Fuck that. I'm going to Berkeley and I won't get to do this for a while.
我得坐前面
I'm sitting in the front.
杰…去吧 我没事
J, just go, OK? I'll live.
不能扔下你一个人
You're not gonna sit by yourself.
好了 用男人的方式解决问题
All right, you know what? We'll just settle this like real men.
这样如何？赌哪面？
How about that? Hmm? Call it.
正面
Heads.
该死！
Shit! Damn it.
好吧 去他妈的 还不是在同一辆车上
All right, fine, what the fuck. It's the same ride, right?
去吧 宝贝
Go. Go ahead. Bye, babe.
嗨 帮兄弟个忙
Hey, uh, just do me a favor.
关照一下她 行不？她有点害怕
Keep an eye on her, OK? She's kinda freaked out.
- 好吧？- 没问题
- Oh. Cool. - All right?
包在我身上
Yeah. Boom, buddy. No problem.
走咯！
Here we go. Hey!
杰 管好你的手
J! Keep your hands to yourself, man.
我是认真的
I'm serious. You know, payback's a bitch, OK?
她或许会需要一些安慰
You know, she might need some comforting…
我会安慰她 好吗？
and I'll be there for her. OK?
嘿 不 出来 出来
Hey, no! No. Get out. Get out.
嘿 找别的舱位吧 演壮志凌云吗
Hey! Find another cockpit, Top Gun.
不要 出来
No. Get…
我们就坐到后面去吧 好吗？
Let's just get in the back, OK?
看看谁回来了？
Guess who's back?
嗨！
Hey!
终点见！
I'll meet you at the end.
快来！好！
Here! All right!
酷！
Cool!
嘿…你们几个小子怎么混进来的？
Hey. How'd you guys get in here?
怎么了？我55尺高了
What? I'm 55 inches.
- 得了 出来 - 唉…
- Sure. Come on out. - Oh, man.
你也是 出来
You, too. Out.
- 准备好了？- 噢！
- Ready? - Ohh!
我说了我们混不进来的
I told you we wouldn't get away with it.
你没事吧？
You OK?
还是玩碰碰车去吧
Let's go on the bumper cars.
来 过来
Come on. Here we go.
耶！
Yeah!
怎么了 我这儿没问题
What's up, man? I'm good.
让我看看你们香甜的乳头
Dare you to, uh, flash me them sweet, sweet titties…
就等转圈道的时候啦
when we go through the loop.
好了 哈！
All right. Ha ha!
嘿！你看不懂…？
Yo! What, you can't read?
禁止携带易松动物品 禁止拍摄
no loose objects! no cameras!
噢 那我装包里可以么
Oh. Well, can I just put it in my pocket, man?
- 没问题吧？- 好吧
- ls that cool? - Yeah.
多谢 哥们儿 不好意思啊
Yeah? Cool. Thanks, buddy. Sorry.
啊 见鬼
Aw, shit!
出发吧！
Here you go!
喔！
Whoo-ooh!
喔！冲啊！宝贝 冲吧！
Whoo! Win, baby! Yes, baby! Win!
来吧！
Come on!
来吧！过把瘾！
Come on. Get hyped.
第一个坡超高的
The first hill's so high.
是啊
Yeah.
要的就是这感觉！
This is what we need!
- 耶…！- 耶…！
- Yeah! - Yeah!
喔！
Whoo!
- 来吧… - 冲啊！
- Let's do this! - Just win!
喔！爽！
Whoo! Shit!
天哪！
Oh, man.
我的天！
Oh, my God!
开始啦！
Here we go!
老天！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
给我来个「波涛汹涌」！
Yeah! Show me your titties!
- 去你妈的 弗兰基！- 噢！
- Fuck off, Frankie! - Oh!
不好！
Oh, shit!
天啊！我们会掉下去的！
Oh, my God! We're gonna fall off!
不要！
No!
- 哟荷 - 凯文！
- Yow! - Kevin!
不！
No!
埃琳 抓牢了！
Erin, hang on!
埃琳！
Erin!
- 抓紧它！- 别放手！
- Hang on! - Don't let go!
我抓不住了！
I can't.
不！
No!
天啊！
Oh, God!
抓稳了 温
Hang on, Wen.
抓稳了 和我一起摇！
Hang on! Help me rock it!
快动了 慢慢地
Almost got it! Gently.
不…
No!
嘿！你看不懂…？
Yo. What, you can't read?
噢 那我装包里可以么
Oh, well. I'll just… I'll put it in my pocket, OK?
好吧
Yeah.
多谢 哥们儿
Thanks, bro.
好了 温 让我们…
Ahh. All right. Let's do this, Wen…
你干什么…
What're you…
出发吧！
Here you go!
耶！冲吧！
Yeah! Let's do it, baby! Whoo!
我们得下去！
We have to get off of here.
别按按钮！别！
No, don't push the button! Don't! Don't push the button!
放我走！快放我走！
Unh! Let me off! Let me off!
温…没事的 一下就过去了…
Wen, Wen! It's all right. Jesus, it's gonna be over…
会翻车的 要翻车！
No! It's gonna crash! It's gonna crash!
温迪？
Wendy?
液压管会破裂的…！轨道也…也要垮！求求你…
The hydraulics will rupture! The tracks'll collapse! Please!
- 怎么回事？- 让我下去！
- What's going on? - Let me off!
这妞发疯了
Chick's on somethin'.
…没事的 你不会有事的
It's all right! You'll be OK!
好了 让他们下去 打开后面那几排
OK, let 'em out. Just the back.
温！温迪！
Wen. Hey! Wendy!
喔！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
放轻松 怎么回事？
Relax. Now, what's the matter?
我看到了一切 在我脑子里
I saw it. I saw it in my head.
轨道垮了 云霄飞车摔成碎片…
The tracks collapsed. The roller coaster crashed.
没事 她刚才就是有点紧张
No, she was just a little upset before.
嘿 你能不能管好这妞？
Man, please, can you please control that bitch?
见她的鬼！什么「液压管…飞车摔得粉碎…」
Damn."It's gonna crash! The hydraulics, the coaster!"
这贱人就是想吸引大家眼球！
Man, she's just trying to get some fuckin' attention.
你知道吗 刘易斯？你他妈就狗屎一砣
You know what? You're a real piece of shit, Lewis.
- 操你妈的！- 操我？
- Fuck you. - Fuck moi?
- 操你妈的！- 别碰我！
- No, man, fuck you! - Don't touch me.
噢！
Ow!
别打了！
Just relax!
打啊！
Fight, man!
嘿！让我下去
Hey. Hey. Let me out.
谁也不许下去！
Nobody else gets off this ride!
老兄 让我下去
Dude, let me off.
真是长不大
So high school.
走吧
Let's out.
- 大家不要慌！- 离他远点！
- Calm down! - Get off of him!
- 放手！- 伊安！
- Relax! - lan!
小姐们去哪里？这正有好戏看…
Where you ladies going? There's a fight.
把他弄出去！大家不要惊慌！
Get him out of here! Hey! Calm down! Relax!
老兄 让我下去 我得看看她有没有事
Dude, let me off. I gotta make sure she's OK.
- 好了！不要闹了！- 嘿！我们走！
- Relax! Calm down! - Hey! Ho! Let's go
- 把你的手拿开！- 出去！
- Get your big ass off me, man! - Hey, ho, let's go!
- 让我下去！- 嘿哟！快点走！
- Let me out! - Hey, ho, let's go!
嘿！
Dude!
嘿哟！快点走！
? Hey, ho, let's go, hey, ho, let's go?
- 嘿哟！快点走！- 让我下去！
- Here we go! - Let me off!
嘿哟！快点走！
? Hey, ho
伙计 那是我女朋友！
Dude, that's my girlfriend!
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
停下来！快停下！
Stop it! No! Stop it!
停下！求求你！轨道会垮的！
Stop it! Please! Please, the tracks are broken.
停下！求求你！
Stop! Stop! Please!
杰森！
Jason!
放松点 好么？
Hey, just relax, OK?
- 求求你！- 她没事 别动手
- Please! - Ease up, man. She's all right.
让她自己静一静
OK? Just let her settle down.
回家安静去吧 听着…
She can settle down at home! Now listen…
你家里电话多少？
what is your home phone number?
我们会给你妈妈打电话 一切都会没事的
OK, we're gonna call your mother. Everything will be taken care of…
啊！
Aah!
天哪！杰森！
Oh, my God! Jason!
嗨 温迪
Hey, Wendy!
嗨！
Hey!
等等 温迪！
Wait! Wendy!
温…等等！
Hey! Hey, Wen. Wait.
我有话跟你讲
I need…I need to talk to you about something.
我只是来领毕业证
Just here to pick up my diploma.
你不参加毕业典礼了？
You're not going to graduation?
不去了
No.
听着 从那该死的地方出来的 不是只有你一个
Look, you're not the only one in a fucked up place, OK?
我是说 也许…
God, I mean, I just thought maybe…
同有异样感觉的人在一起 也许会好些
it'd be good for you to be somewhere where other people feel the same way.
在毕业典礼上？
At graduation?
谢了 我参加的葬礼够多了
No. Thanks. I've had enough funerals.
就算是为了杰和卡丽
Then do it for J and Carrie.
为他们做什么？人死了…
Do what? If you die, then there's nothing…
就是死了 什么都不知道了
then you're just dead, and they don't know.
他们要是真到了天堂 同圣人们在一起
And if they are up in Heaven with Lincoln and Gandhi…
你以为谁还会在乎一个破毕业典礼？
do you think they really care about our high school graduation? No.
连我这个活人都不在乎
I am alive, and I don't care.
等我开车离开这里…
As soon as I pull out of that parking lot…
从此就和麦金利学校没有任何关系
I am so out of McKinley.
没有了杰 还有什么值得留恋的？
Without J, what's here for me?
还有我呢
I'm here. OK?
我向杰保证会照顾你
I made a promise to J that I would take care of you.
坐云霄飞车 3分钟
On the ride. For 3 minutes.
没叫你照顾我一辈子
You weren't making the promise for a lifetime.
凯文…
Kevin…
不是看在杰和你是哥们儿…
if it wasn't for you and J being friends…
而我和卡丽又是好朋友
and me and Carrie being friends…
我们俩都不会再一起走
we wouldn't have even hung out.
我们都不欣赏对方
We don't even like each other.
伊安·麦金利
"lan McKinley."
看我这破姓
How pathetic is it that my last name…
一看就是个高中生
is the same as my high school?
茱丽 快看我找谁签名了
Julie, look who I got to sign my yearbook.
- 不会吧 真棒！- 是啊
- No way. Nice. - Yeah.
是不是要邀请她？
I think we should invite her.
- 要吗？- 是的
- You think? - Yeah.
温 这个…
Wen? Um…
我们准备去今晚的毕业典礼…
So we're ready for graduation tonight…
等会儿我们要去日光浴沙龙…
we're going to the tanning salon after this…
你要是想一起去 我们完全没意见
and we are so totally cool if you wanna come with.
千真万确
Totally.
就聊聊天什么的
And just like, talk if you want.
这是我手机号
Here's my cell.
我已有你手机号
I already have your number.
我们真是善良啊
That was so nice of us.
你不是一个人
You're not alone.
天啊 我很感激大家的好心
God, I appreciate everyone trying to help.
好吧 我真的感激
OK? I really do.
不是这个 之前也有类似的事故
No, it's happened before.
为了找到合理的解释我上网查了
OK? I went online looking for an explanation about…
温迪 听我一句好吗？
Wendy, just…just listen to me, all right?
好 听着 我上网查了
All right, look, I went online looking for an explanation…
为什么会发生这一切 我查到…
about what happened, and I found out…
纽约一个高中法语班
about this high school French class from New York.
6年前 他们去巴黎旅游
Six years ago they went on a trip to Paris.
在登机的时候
When they were boarding…
其中一个孩子产生了飞机爆炸的幻觉
a kid had a vision that the plane was gonna explode.
就像你当时那样
Just like you did.
他害怕极了
He freaked out…
有7个人同时下了飞机
and seven people got off the plane.
就像我们
Just like us.
起飞后不久 180航班就坠毁了
And on takeoff, Flight 180 blew up.
接下去的几个月
And over the next several months…
所有从飞机上下来的人 都相继死于离奇的事故
everyone who got off that plane started dying in weird accidents.
死亡的顺序 就是他们在飞机上座位的顺序
They died in the order they would've if they had stayed on the plane.
除非有人干预 然后死神就跳过他们
Unless someone intervened, then it skipped them.
去死吧 凯文
Fuck you, Kevin.
温迪 温迪！
W-Wendy! Wendy! Hey!
每次我们来这儿都是这样
Ohh, every time we come here.
我在想要不要做20分钟的米勒
I was thinking of going for 20 minutes in the Muller.
上次参加葬礼前做了 效果很好
We did that for all the funerals and it turned out amazing.
是啊 但才过了没几个礼拜
Yeah, but that was just a couple of weeks ago, though.
我是说 我们的皮肤还算古铜
I mean, we're still pretty bronzed.
我想 我们也许做个综合调理吧
I was just thinking we could go for, like, a tune-up.
我只是希望能以最漂亮的方式出场
I just wanna make sure that we look our best.
是啊
Yeah.
知道吗 那天晚上死掉的人
You know, for all those kids that died that night…
他们永远不能参加毕业典礼了
who will never get a graduation.
知道吗 你说的对
You know what? You're totally right.
- 我很难过 - 嗯
- I'm sorry. - Mmm.
那是我的 我的幸运手链
This is my…my good guy luck bracelet…
祖母在遗嘱里写了留给我的
that Grandma left me in her will.
茱丽
Julie?
我需要它
I need…
它能给我帮助
I could use some help.
对于杰森 我感到很自责
I have such… such guilt over Jason.
我不该让车开动
I should never have let that ride go.
上帝 我平时是那么有控制欲
God. I'm usually such a control freak…
但我却没有尽力去阻止这件事
but I didn't do enough to stop it.
无论如何我都该阻止的
I should've done everything I could to stop it.
我愿意付出一切
And I would give anything…
如果能给我一次机会重来
to have a second chance.
但不可能了
But I never can.
我不希望有一天 我对你也产生这样的愧疚感 茱丽
I don't want to some day feel that way about you, Julie.
我是说 我和妈妈爸爸谈不到一块儿去
I mean, I can't talk to Mom and Dad.
我只有你了
You're all I have left.
如果我找到地方搬出去
You think when I find a place…
也许你能来和我一起住一阵子？
maybe you could come stay with me for a while?
你知道我会的
You know I will.
你…
You…
先保管它
keep this now…
我去看你的时候要回
and I'll get it when I come see you.
哦 对了 那个…
Oh. And…hey, how 'bout on your end?
我能借照相机用吗 为了今晚的毕业典礼？
Can I use the school camera for graduation tonight?
当然 不过礼拜一一定要带来学校
Yeah. As long as you bring it back to school on Monday.
成交
Done.
其实 电量有点低了
Actually, the battery is pretty low…
不如你先去准备 我给它充会儿电
so why don't you go get ready, and I'll recharge it a bit.
酷
Cool.
我们赶时间 犹利
ln a hurry, Yuri.
抱歉 抱歉 手机在室内根本没信号
Sorry, sorry. Cell phone signal is shit in here.
我想是阳光浴床干扰了信号
I think tanning beds mess with signal.
我只好到外面去听
I must go outside.
为什么不用电话？
Why don't you just use that phone?
我是想啊 但她说起来就没完 老板非宰了我不可
I would, but she talks forever, then my boss gives me shit.
见鬼 又是她
Shit. That's her.
你出去听吧
You know what? Just go outside.
我们自己能搞定
We can deal with this ourselves.
好吧
OK.
嘿 这次别在房间里喝饮料了 好吗？
Hey. No drinks in the room this time, OK?
好极了
Good.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我不想有人进来看见我的裸体
Nobody is walking in here and seein' me naked.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
他说了不要带饮料进来 如果溅出来了…
Dude, he said no drinks. If you spill that shit…
他们得像上次一样清扫一遍
we're gonna have to clean it up like last time.
行了吧 不会溅出来
Happy, beyotch? Nothing to spill.
犹利干嘛把温度调那么低？
Why does Yuri keep it so cold in here?
也许这些机器必须保持低温也说不定
Maybe it's supposed to be colder for the machines or whatever.
开高几度不会怎么样吧
Oh, a few degrees won't hurt.
（此设备使用强度不可超过250伏特交流电）
糟糕 我忘带iPod了
Shit! I forgot my iPod.
确实很糟
Sucks, bitch.
他们这有CD的
They got CDs.
席琳的？
Ew. Celine?
还是布兰妮？
Britney?
天哪 到这儿来的人中 我们是不是唯一跟得上潮流的？
Dude, are we like the only cool people that come here or what?
是啊
Uh, yeah.
随便听吧
Ugh. Whatever.
你干嘛还穿内裤？
Why are you wearing underwear?
斯坦梅说 他看到晒痕就兴奋
Steinmetz says he gets off on tan lines.
好吧
All right.
云霄飞车
Roller coaster
爱之车
Of love
怎么说的
Say what
云霄飞车
Roller coaster
对…
Right
爱之车
Of love
云霄飞车
Roller coaster
云霄飞车 爱之车
Roller coaster of love
云霄飞车
Roller coaster
云霄飞车 爱之车
Roller coaster of love…
我
I
哼…哼…
? Huh, huh
要与你同行 女孩
I'm gonna ride, girl
喔…
Whoo.
云霄飞车 爱之车
Roller coaster of love
最爱云霄飞车 女孩
? Love roller coaster, girl?
云霄飞车
Roller coaster
世界太乱 我只爱你
Lovin' you in a freaky world, child
云霄飞车 爱之车
Roller coaster of love
相机充好电了？
Camera charged?
哦 抱歉 完全没电了
Oh, um, sorry, the battery's totally dead.
没法开机 不好意思
Camera's not working. Sorry.
茱丽 我需要时间
Look, Julie, I need a minute, OK?
一个人静一静
Like private.
云霄飞车 感觉真棒！
That feels nice, roller coaster
再来一次
One more time
云霄飞车 爱之车
Roller coaster of love
云霄飞车
Roller coaster
云霄飞车 爱之车
Roller coaster of love
好像有点热过头了
It's way too warm in here now, huh?
见鬼 我把温度调太高了
I fucked up. I set it too hot in here.
什么？
Huh?
喂？
Hello?
- 嘿 阿什丽 是我温迪 - 美体中！请留言
- Hey, Ashley, it's Wendy… - Psych! Leave a message.
嘿 阿什丽 是我温迪
Hi, Ashley, this is Wendy.
你们弄完后给我回个电话
Gimme a call whenever you guys are done.
还有再次感谢你们邀请我
And thanks again for the invite.
- 有人帮忙吗？- 啊！
- Someone help! - Aah!
对不起我打晚了
Sorry I was too late.
嘿 开门
Hey, open the door!
救命啊
Help me!
有时我们觉得生命难以掌握
We may feel that our lives are not our own.
似乎死神掌管着我们生命的轨迹
That Death controls, frames our lives.
出生即是死亡的序曲
Our birth's nothing but death begun.
然而 不管是年轻生命消逝的悲剧
Yet, whether it is with this tragic loss of young lives…
使我们悲伤不已
which we have suffered much of late…
还是在夜晚安详逝去的老者
or with the soft passing of the elderly in the night…
我们在死神的眼里都是平等的
we are all equal in Death's eyes.
「在死神眼里是平等的」？
"Equal in Death's eyes?"
所有人吗？你怎么能这么说？
All of us? How can you say that?
闭嘴 麦金利！
Shut up, McKinley.
伙计 想想吧 查理·曼森活到了70岁
Dude, think it through. Charlie Manson made it to 70.
- 阿萨马呢？还活着 - 我们走
- Osama? Still kickin'. - Let's go.
拉皮条的 副总统 到处活动
Pimps, vice-presidents walking around.
- 他们所犯了的种种罪恶… - 我们走吧 快走
- All the atrocities they've committed… - Let's just go. Come on.
却还好好活着
they're alive and well.
那两个女孩 她们从没害过人
These two girls, who'd never done shit to anybody…
- 嘘 - 连18岁都活不到
- Shh! - They don't get to make it to 18?
他妈的平等在哪里？
Where's the fucking equality in that?
- 说啊？- 走吧 老兄
- What? - Come on, man.
我可以 我没事
I can…Yeah. Fine.
我没事 好了
Fine. All right. All right.
我很好 行了
I'm fine. All right.
简直疯了
That's crazy.
想要对逝者做最后追忆的人…
Those of you who would like to pay a final remembrance…
请上前来
please step forward at this time.
我觉得都是我的错
I so feel this is so my fault.
怎么可能是你的错？
How could it possibly be your fault?
只把女人当作玩乐的工具
Seein' women as nothin' but fun bags.
如果我能看到她们…
I mean…if l'd've seen their…
人性的一面…
whatever…humanity…
她们也不会为了要外表漂亮 而感到那么大压力了
they wouldn't have felt the pressure to look so good.
为了吸引弗兰基 去减肥 去除臭
lmpress Franklin Cheeks. Go on diets. Deodorize.
去健身 去晒日光浴
Stretch. Tan.
别难过 弗兰基
Don't be down, Frankie.
你该为你能把所有事…
Be proud of your ability to make everything…
都归到你头上的能力 感到骄傲
that happens somehow a story about you.
上帝
God!
事情确实糟透了 兄弟
Yo, man. These things really suck, man.
真他妈无聊
Fucking boring.
如果下次你来参加我的葬礼…
Hey, if you ever have to come to my funeral…
给我带个掌上游戏机什么的
man, bring me a PSP or somethin'.
至少我能有点事做
'Least I have somethin' to do then.
喂？
Hello?
我在杰的墓旁
I'm with J.
你怎么在这哭鼻子？
What are you doing up here in the nosebleeds?
我可以把你排在第二排
You know, I could've gotten you second row.
我不想在那儿加剧别人的痛苦
I didn't want to upset anyone by being there.
我想如果我呆在这儿 也许能感到杰的…
And I wondered if maybe here I could feel J's…
灵魂或者看到他现身
spirit or presence or…
之类的
whatever.
但现在我在这里…
But now that I'm here…
却感到了死后根本没有灵魂 这种感觉从未有过
if there's any place that makes me feel like there's no life after death…
这是公墓
it's a cemetery.
是啊 我也没有感觉到凯丽的灵魂
Yeah, I haven't felt Carrie's spirit either.
我试过了
And I've tried.
很努力的试
Real hard. Heh.
我想也许他的灵魂在那晚…
I thought maybe he's been with me since…
我们上车之前 就已经和我在一起了
that night… before I got on the ride…
杰森说的…
Jason said…
上帝 就是那句话使我同意上车
God, and it was just to get me on the ride…
他说…
he said…
「你害怕的是不能控制」
"Your fear is from a sense of having no control."
他说的那一刻我就感觉到害怕
And I've felt that fear since the moment he said it.
也许那也是导致幻觉的原因
Even thought it maybe somehow caused the hallucination…
但这种害怕不仅仅是感到恐惧
but this fear is more than just being scared.
像是感到某种东西的存在
It's like a presence.
就像有东西一直跟随着我
Like a living thing always with me.
你觉得那是杰？
You think it's J?
不 我知道不是
No, I know it's not.
和杰在我身边完全不同的感觉
This presence is the opposite of how J made me feel.
又冷 又可怕
It's cold and terrifying.
这是林肯照的最后一张照片
That's the last photograph Lincoln posed for.
底片被划破了
The photographic plate was broken…
造成了一条无法抹去的痕迹
causing a line that can't be removed.
这里就是他中弹的地方
Exactly where he was shot.
看这个 看到阴影了吗？
Look. See the shadow?
但这些照片和我们有什么关系？
But what do these pictures have to do with us?
这张照片照于…
Look. This occurred one year to the day…
180航班出事的一年前 看到路上的标记吗？
of the Flight 180 disaster. Look at the road sign.
我想你和我说这些
Look, I guess you came to me with this…
是不是因为我该为告诉你…
because I'm responsible for putting this in your head…
180航班的事负责
with the Flight 180 thing.
它确实发生了 说不定也发生在我们周围
And it did happen, and it may be occurring here…
但你不能相信所有古怪的事
but you can't believe every weird thing out there…
就因为你绝望的想找一个答案
because you're desperate for an answer.
这些是我拍的
I took these.
那天晚上的
That night.
这些？
These?
就这些吗？
Are these it?
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit.
Oh…shit.
没事吧
Whoa, whoa, hey. You all right?
我有些虚脱
I'm feeling a little woozy.
你多久没吃东西了？
When was the last time you ate?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
好吧 来 我开车
All right, come on. I'll drive.
那些曾经在180航班上 之后死于事故的孩子们…
OK, those kids on Flight 180 died in accidents…
他们是按照在飞机上的座位顺序 相继出事的
in the order they would've died if they'd have stayed on the plane.
好吧 要真是这样…
OK? So if this is that, then…
那阿什丽姐妹后面就是弗兰基
then Frankie was behind Ashlyn and Ashley.
当我看到阿什丽姐妹的照片时…
When I saw Ashley and Ashlyn's picture…
我本能的感到…
I felt this instinct.
似乎照片中有某种暗示 我甚至
Like there was a hint in the picture. I even…
甚至给她们打了电话 看能不能阻止悲剧发生
I even called to see if I could keep them from going.
弗兰基的照片是什么样的？
Well, what's Frankie's picture look like?
就在这儿
It's right here.
- 你拍到了？- 对
- You got it? - Yeah.
- 小心！- 噢！
- Wait! Watch out! - Oh!
嘿 你疯了吗？
Hey! Hey! Are you crazy?
抱歉！
Sorry!
好了 就在那儿吃吧
All right, let's just eat over there.
一直开 开到底
And go through the drive through.
我不想任何人听到我们的谈话内容
I don't want anyone hearing what we're talking about.
很高兴看到这件事没有…
Well, it's nice to see that things haven't made you…
减少你的控制癖
any less of a control freak.
- 找到了吗？- 是的
- You got it? - Yeah, all right.
这是弗兰基的照片
Here's Frank's picture.
好的
All right.
很明显 他正从梯子上滑下来
Well, this is obvious. He's falling off a ladder.
一个绳梯 也许他会吊死
A rope ladder, though. Maybe he might hang.
听着 也许没那么夸张 好吧
Look, or maybe it's not that literal. All right, what's…
会不会和这些奖品有关系？
Could there be anything in these prizes?
难道他会被一个 超大的海绵宝宝撞死？
Oh, what, like he's gonna get crushed by a giant Spongebob?
海绵宝宝住在水底下
Hey, Spongebob lives underwater.
原来这个你还知道啊
It's so sad that you know that.
行了 他赢了一条傻里傻气的 胶皮女人项链…
All right. He won that tacky mud-flap girl chain…
就在玩这游戏的时候 但是…
on this game, though, so…
那种胶皮不是通常都用在 18轮巨型卡车上的吗？
aren't those usually on those big 18 wheelers?
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
上帝 在照片上找不出什么卡车
God, I don't see it in this picture anywhere though.
知道了 上帝
All right! God.
行了
All right.
请问您需要点餐吗？
Uh, can I take your order?
是的 你想吃什么？
Yeah. What do you want?
你没事吧？
Are you OK?
你的无线电是短路了吧
Please tell me there's a short in your wiring.
喔 那辆车靠太近了
Whoa. Whoa. That guy's way too close to my truck.
嘿 你他妈太近了 往前拉点
Hey, you're too fucking close, man! Pull up!
嘿！
Hey!
有人
There is someone
停车 停车！
Stop! Stop!
走在你身后
Walking behind you
小心 见鬼！
Watch out! Shit!
- 他妈的 - 转过身
- What the fuck? - Turn around
- 哦 上帝！- 看着我
- Oh, my God! - Look at me?
- 下车！下车 - 什么？怎么了？
- Get out! Get out! - What? What?
我们后面！
Behind us!
卡车没人在驾驶！
There's no one in that truck!
看着你的脚步
Watching your footsteps
见鬼！往前开！往前开！
Shit! Hey! Pull up, man! Come on! Pull up!
- 看着我 - 哦 该死的！
- Look at me - Unh! Shit!
- 有人 - 倒车
- There is someone - Back up!
倒车！
Back up!
谁真心爱你
Who really loves you
让你看我的真心
Here's my heart
小心 小心
Watch your eyes! Watch your eyes! Come here!
在我的手中
? ln my hand?
转过身
? Turn around?
- 看着我 - 快 我们走！
- Look at me - Come on. Let's go!
快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on.
我们都清理完了 你们要搭车吗？
We're all done here. You need a ride?
我们可以走回到我家…
Um, we can walk to my house…
然后我开车送你回去
and then I'll give you a ride to yours.
不用了 谢谢 一切都会过去的
No, thanks. We'll be OK.
是不是？
Will we?
是的 我们会逃过去
Yeah. We'll be all right.
我是说…
I mean…
弗兰基那样…
how Frank…
上帝啊 这不仅仅是恐怖
God, it…it's not only horrible…
你能感到吗… 能感到这有多么邪恶
but can you feel… can you feel how vicious it was?
放松
Easy.
OK? Easy.
我们…
Let's just…
我们先退一步想
let's just take a step back.
好吗？在云霄车上他是坐在阿什丽姐妹后面
All right? He was behind Ashley and Ashlyn on the ride…
但是没有梯子 也没有绳子
but there was no ladder here. You know, there was no rope.
照片上没有预示这种情况
Nothing in that picture pointed to this.
我们想错了
We were wrong about the photos.
我不该来这儿 还不如什么也不知道的好
I should've left town. It's better not knowing.
不 被蒙在鼓里永远没有好处
No, it's never better staying ignorant.
被蒙在鼓里等于交出了控制权
Willful ignorance is surrendering control.
怎么 这句话是布鲁克先生的 英语课上学来的吗？
What, did you read that somewhere in Mrs. Brooks' English class?
不 知道吗 我不是
No. l…you know, I'm not…
像你想象的那样愚蠢透顶
I'm not the total idiot you think I am.
好了 弗兰基后面是刘易斯…
OK, that's Lewis after Frank…
然后是依安和埃琳
then lan and Erin.
有几个孩子在他们后面 但我看不清楚…
There's a couple of kids behind them, but I can't make them out…
这家伙的手挡住了 你看得清吗？
because this guy's arm's in the way. Can you?
不
No.
好 知道吗？
All right, you know what?
我们可以问问刘易斯 依安和埃琳 看他们是不是记得
We'll ask Lewis, lan, and Erin if they remember.
怎么样？
OK?
还有没有其他拍到云霄飞车的照片？
Are there any more pictures from the roller coaster?
我想…
I guess…
那些事迟早会发生在我们身上
that kind of thing is gonna happen to us
发生在剩下还活着的人身上
for the rest of our lives.
是的
Yeah.
知道吗 我本想…
You know, I was gonna…
本想向她求婚的
I was gonna ask her to marry me.
一毕业就求婚
Right after graduation.
不 等等
No, wait.
在史黛西后面
Look, behind Stacy.
是弗兰基
That's Frank.
照片告诉了我们他的死亡方式
This picture shows how he died.
再看刘易斯那张
All right, go back to Lewis.
他拿着锤子
OK, he's got that hammer.
那个重力砣正落下来 好像要砸在…
And the weight looks like it's coming down…
他的头上
on his head.
不 看看这个
No, no, no, check this out.
现在刘易斯正在州队的训练营里
Right now Lewis is down at State for football training camp.
州队的名字就叫苏丹
State's team is called the Sultans.
就是这个 这就是线索
That's it. That's the clue.
我们得告诉他 给他看照片
We have to tell him. Show him these pictures.
你想知道什么？
Wouldn't you want to know?
我们也有照片吗？
Wait, there's pictures of us in there?
有
Yeah.
当然有
Yeah, of course.
不
Huh. No.
不 我不想看我的
No. I don't want to see mine. No. Huh.
你不是说不想被蒙在鼓里？
What about willful ignorance?
当我在放屁 行了吗？
Well, I'm full of shit, all right?!
我是说 我从没想过 我会看到自己是怎么死的…
I mean, I never thought I could see my own death…
在我还没死前 温迪
before it happened, Wendy.
知道吗 我们可以去告诉刘易斯 但是…
No, you know what? We can tell Lewis, but…
说真的 如果真有什么能打败死神…
Seriously, if there's any way to beat this thing…
我一定会尽全力找出来…
I gotta stay focused…
但如果我看了自己的照片 我只会被吓迷糊
and if I look at that picture, all I'm gonna do is obsess.
所以 我不想看
So, you know what? No, I don't want to see it.
我是说 除非到了不得不看的时候
I mean, unless we have to.
你是说当轮到我们的时候
You mean until we have to.
还有件事
One more thing.
很糟糕吗？
ls it bad?
我是说是不是很痛苦或者很难堪？
I mean, is it, like, painful or embarrassing?
我是说 没有屁股朝天之类的吧
I mean, there's nothing, like, up my ass or anything, right?
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
你有病 你们都有
You on crack. Both of you.
先听我们说 好吗？先是阿什丽姐妹
Just listen, OK? Ashley and Ashlyn were first.
然后是弗兰基 接着是你 这是…
Then Frankie Cheeks and then you. This is the…
- 少来了 凯文 - 听着
- Aw, come on, Kevin. - Listen.
麦金利和埃琳是下一对
McKinley and Erin were next, all right?
还有两个人在我们前面 你记得是谁吗？
And there were two people in front of us. Do you remember who they were?
见鬼 不知道 我也不在乎 你也没必要管这些 老兄…
Fuck no, and I don't care. And you shouldn't care either, man…
因为你刚才说的那些 在我听来是胡说八道
'cause what you're tellin' me right now is straight bullshit.
听我说 刘易斯
Just listen, Lewis.
凯文 听过那些故事吗
Kevin, it's like those stories.
一个男人被车撞死 而这车正是10年前被他卖掉的车
Like this guy was killed by a car he sold 10 years ago.
两姐妹 她们同时被撞死 而她们正分别在开车去碰面的路上
Two sisters, right, were killed when they were driving to visit each other.
知道吗 就像这类型的屁事
You know, shit like that, man.
去死吧 黑熊！
Fuck the Bruins!
去死吧 黑熊
Oh, yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
黑熊的白痴们！
Bruin faggots!
去死吧 黑熊
Yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
老兄 你以为是在看传说故事吗？
Man, you're reading into this shit like them damn urban legends.
3个人死了 刘易斯
Three people have died, Lewis.
如果你觉得这件事简单到…
I mean, if you think this can be written off…
可以用巧合来解释…
as a simple coincidence and it ends there…
你们却拒绝承认
you're in serious denial.
那你们两个呢？
Unh! What about you two, huh?
什么？
What?
你们俩的朋友都那么倒霉的死了
You both lost people real close to you in a fucked-up way.
为了减少罪恶感或者别的什么…
And in order to feel less guilty or whatever…
就说看到什么记号死亡方式
seeing signs and patterns, man.
我不想怪你们 但这是错的
I don't blame you. But it's wrong, dawg.
是错的
Unh! It's wrong.
我无法接受
That's denial.
懂了吗？
You got it!
好吧 那云霄飞车事件怎么解释？
OK, what about what happened at the roller coaster? Huh?
温迪都看到了
Wendy saw it.
老兄 她不是有预感吗
Man, she got a hunch. Fuckin' intense, but she got a hunch.
我干这行也是因为我有预感
Man, I'm here because I get good hunches before every down.
不 你知道他们逃不过去
No, you know they're either gonna run or pass.
而她的预感是不受她控制的
Hers came to her from nowhere.
你因为她而幸存着
You're here and alive because of her.
不 我活着是因为我自己
No, I'm alive because of me.
不 听着 你还没明白
No, listen. You don't get it, man.
这对你有意义吗？
Does that make sense to you?
一点意义都没有 凯文 这都是胡说八道
There's nothing to get, Kevin! It's bullshit.
不 听我说好吗
No, just hear me out, all right?
说到幻觉 我能看到我一生…
Talk about a vision. Man, I seen my whole life played out…
死神取不了我的命
and it sure as hell ain't gonna end now. Unh!
我的活法就像我预料到的那样
It's going just as I saw it.
35场高校比赛 没有受任何伤
35 high school games without an injury.
- 美国队全是美国人 - 二队
- USA Today All-American. - Second team.
- 为苏丹打球 - 黑熊会赢你们
- Free ride to play for the Sultans! - The Bruins passed on you.
去死吧
Man, fuck the Bruins!
- 扁死他们 - 他妈的说得对
- Fuck 'em! - You goddamn right!
黑熊算什么东西
What the fuck is a Bruin anyway?
四年后…
Four years from now…
刘易斯·罗门路一定会进到 奥克兰的第二轮比赛
Lewis Romero goin' in the second round to Oakland.
他要玩死对手
He's gonna romp and stomp.
15个赛季 他要带上拳王的戒指
15 seasons, with four Super Bowl rings on his fingers.
刘易斯不怕死 去你的死神吧
Lewis ain't afraid of no death. Fuck Death!
死神是他妈丹佛的拳迷
Death is a fuckin' Denver fan.
穿着蓝色和桔色的衣服
Death wear blue and orange.
真正的男人会穿黑色
Real men wear black.
刘易斯不怕死神
Lewis ain't afraid of no Death.
我要死神怕我
Death is afraid of me!
死神怕我！
Death fears me!
凯文
Kevin.
我会赢 我会赢
'Cause, baby, I just win. I just win, Kevin!
我只知道 我会赢
That's all I know how to do! I just win! Unh!
去他妈的死神
Fuck Death!
- 去他妈的黑熊 - 对
- Fuck the Bruins! - Yeah!
- 小心 - 刘易斯！
- Look out! - Lewis!
老兄 太近了
Man, that was close, Lewis.
看到了吗
Hey, did you see that?
让我来告诉你 凯文
Whoo! What I tell you, Kevin, huh?
去死吧 死神 我会赢
Fuck Death! I just win!
我就是要赢 凯文
That's all I know how to do, Kevin.
赢！
Baby, I just win!
- 哦！- 上帝啊！
- Ooooh! - God!
是我做错什么吗…
Did I do something…
给大家带来这样的灾难
to bring this on everybody?
别这样 温迪
Don't, Wendy.
可是为什么是我？
But why me?
有那么多人 想要拥有预测未来的能力…
All those people out there wanting to have a premonition…
或者想看到鬼魂什么的 可是我不想
or see a ghost or whatever, and I don't.
我只想让这一切结束
I just want it to stop.
结束
Just stop.
我不知道为什么 温迪…
I don't know why, Wendy…
但你没有做错什么
but you didn't do anything.
好吗？这只是…
All right? This is just…
我说不上来 我是说 我想知道原因
I don't know. I mean, I wish I knew why, you know?
我希望即使能猜一个…
I wish I could…I could come up with a guess even…
能让你觉得好受些 但是…
to make you feel OK, but…
我做不到
You know, I can't.
嗯
Yeah.
我什么也做不了
There's nothing I can do.
你来开车好吗？
Can you drive?
好
Yeah.
顺便问一句 我的那张照片
You know, by the way, that…that picture of me.
我的头 没有穿过挡风玻璃或者怎么样吧？
My, uh, my head's not, like, through the windshield or anything?
或者被方向盘撞碎？
You know, crushed by a steering wheel?
或者被排档杆刺穿？
lmpaled by a gear shift?
是不是？
Right?
呼叫泽普 我是皮普
Zip, it's Pip.
那些夹板割的怎么样了？
Have you cut those plywood orders yet?
我还没开工 皮普
Uh, that's a big no, Pip.
监督人要我先把那些鸽子弄走
Osama bin Supervisor wants me to get rid of these pigeons first.
它们总是弄响警报
They keep settin' off the alarms.
你们好吗 宝贝
Hello, babies.
等我再进货…
Hey. After l, uh, restock this stuff…
那些小客户就不能…
that these pinhead customers can't manage…
自己来还架子了吗？
to return to the shelves themselves…
我们别再干了好吗？
we can blow out of here, OK?
好 宝贝
Righty-o, babe.
埃琳 是温迪和凯文
Erin, it's Wendy and Kevin.
见鬼！
Shit!
你们他妈的把我吓死了！
You scared the shit out of me!
先听我们把话说完
Yeah, wait till you hear what we have to tell you.
呼叫泽普 我是皮普 到这儿来
Zip, it's Pip. Come over here.
你听了会说不出话来
You are gonna trip when you hear this.
你在吊我胃口 皮普 我就来
Well, paint me intrigued, Pip. I'm on my way.
说简单点吧 我会被钉子钉死…
So let me get this straight. I'm gonna O.D. on nail polish…
依安也会死？
and lan is gonna be embarrassed to death?
你看到那天温迪是怎么了 对吧？
You saw what happened to Wendy, right?
还有发生在其他人身上的事 你们看到照片了
What's happened to the others? I mean, you just saw their pictures.
哦 上帝 伙计们 怎么了？
Oh, my God, guys, what's going on?
发生什么了？太吓人了 太吓人了
What's going on? That's crazy! That's crazy!
我们想知道云霄飞车上 坐在你们后面的是谁
We need to know who was sitting behind you on the roller coaster.
在云霄飞车上坐在我们后面的是谁
OK, who was sitting behind us on the roller coaster?
是不是那个被选出来当…
Oh! Oh, wait! Wasn't it that one guy who got voted…
红龙虾西餐店经理的那个人？
most likely to become manager at Red Lobster?
不是 哦 我想起来
Oh, no. You know what? God, I remember.
有个人 穿着黑色斗篷…
There was this guy, uh, black cloak…
但我没看到他的脸…
I didn't see his face, but, um…
服务员没收了他的镰刀…
the ride attendant did take his sickle…
就在开车之前 不知道这个对你们有没有帮助
before the ride started if that's helpful in any way.
你以为我们会在乎你的嘲笑吗？
Do you think we care if you laugh at us?
这关系到我们的命
This is our lives, OK?
我们没有选择 你就直说吧
What choice do we have? Just give into it?
哦 知道吗 根本没有
Oh, God. You know what? There is no "it."
你们的意思是说死神好像一个人吗？
OK, wait, are you guys saying that Death is, like, a person?
不 是一种力量
No. It's like…like a force.
知道吗 力量只是力量
Yeah. Well, you know what? A force is just a force.
没别的 只是能量转换而已
It's nothing else. Just transferred energy.
我是说 力量没有目标性 没有自主意识
I mean, it has no goals, no awareness that is a force.
但这件事有自主意识 麦金利
But there is awareness, McKinley.
根据过去的经验 如果这条线的下一个人获救…
ln fact, in past cases, if the next in line is saved…
这个人就逃脱了死神的索命 这就是我们来这的原因
it'd skip that person. That's why we're here.
哦 老兄 你吸了什么迷药了吗？
Oh, man, what have you been smoking?
- 最上层 - 好嘞
- Top shelf. - OK.
凯文 那些条幅 照片里有
Kevin! Those banners. They're in the picture.
依安 小心那些箱子
lan, watch those boxes!
见鬼 老兄 你说箱子会掉下来
What the fuck, man? You said those boxes were falling!
不 我说小心那些箱子
No, I said watch the boxes.
是吗？干什么？他们什么也干不了
Really? What for? They're not doing anything.
我们只是想救你们 没什么好抱歉的
We're not gonna apologize for trying to save you.
你们还没有看到或经历我们经历的 暂时
You haven't seen or been through what we have…yet.
哦 暂时
Oh. Yet.
理论上你们觉得谁是下一个 我还是依安？
OK, so who's next in this theory you have, me or lan?
我们知道是按照 我们坐云霄飞车的前后顺序…
Well, we know the order of how we were sitting on the roller coaster…
但还不知道坐在一起的人 谁先谁后
but not how it works with people who sat together.
我们不知道阿什丽姐妹是哪个先死的
OK, we don't know if Ashley or Ashlyn died first.
上帝 死神还真会玩复杂
Hmm. God, Death is fucking complicated.
不 知道吗 一点也不复杂
No, you know what? It's not complicated.
很简单 是人都会死
It's simple. People die.
那是生命的一部分
That's just part of life.
事实上 每天有15万人死掉
150, 000 people a day, actually.
知道吗 我是说…
You know? I mean…
我们是生物学上的实体 而死亡只是…
we're biological entities, and death is just…
- 最上层 - 生物功能的终结
- Top shelf. - the end of biological function.
就这么简单
It's as simple as that.
你怎么解释我们遇到的事？
How can you explain what happened to us as simple?
我是说 如果温迪没有预测到…
I mean, if Wendy never had that premonition…
没人下那节车 我们现在都是死人了
and none of us had gotten off that ride, we'd all be dead right now.
- 对你来说无所谓吗？- 哦 是啊
- Does that not make sense to you? - Oh, yeah.
凯文 那些纯粹死于心脏病的人呢？
Kevin, how come when a guy dies of a plain heart attack…
没有人会说…
no one goes, like…
哇 他当时正在吃法国烤面包…
"Oh, wow, he was eating French toast…
而戴安娜王妃正巧在巴黎出车祸…
"when Princess Diana died in Paris…
然后他边看电视转播的葬礼时 就突然死了
"and then he saw her funeral on TV, and now he's dead"?
知道为什么 这听上去就像疯子在说话…
You know why? Because they'd sound crazy…
所以知道你们两个像什么吗？疯子
so guess how you two sound right now? Crazy.
泽普 我干完了 现在你去割夹板吧…
Zip, I'm done. So finish cutting those orders…
- 钉完我们就走 - 好！
- so we can get out of here. - OK!
恶心
Sick.
好了
OK.
就算按照你们的说法
Let's go with what you guys are saying.
比方这样说…
Let's just say, you know…
死神有他的计划…
that Death does have a conscious plan…
这计划开始启动了 好极了
and that it's been set into motion. Great.
那么按照牛顿的第三运动定律…
So, Newton's third law of motion, and, well, look…
我想这定律应该对死神也管用…
I'm just guessing that it goes for Death, too…
既然他是在我们的世界
when he's working in our world.
牛顿说每一个动力 都会有一个反作用力
Newton says that every action has an equal and opposite reaction.
那就是说…
So, that means that…
死神如果采取行动 我们也能
if Death has taken action, so can we.
我们所采取的行动…
And that that action we take might have…
会成为阻止死神计划的反作用力
an opposite reaction that thwarts Death's intent.
你真是个混蛋 但说下去
You're being a fucker, but go on.
好 好
OK. OK.
比如…
What if, for example…
在死神列表的最后一个人 做了一个很功利主义的选择…
the last in line were to make the utilitarian choice…
比如自杀 那会怎样？
Kill themselves.
喔 那绝对会坏了死神的计划…
Wow! Wow! That's pretty much gonna ruin any plan…
更妙的是…
that Death's put in motion. And even better…
被跳过的5个人就得救了
hey, it's gonna save five skipped lives.
有人反对吗？
Any takers?
不 我不这么认为
Nah, I didn't think so.
那个 小心！
There! Those!
我什么也没说 我觉得…
I didn't say anything. I mean, I think…
他们想吓唬我们让我们说出来…
they were trying to scare us into saying something…
但他们没理由监禁我们
but they had nothing to keep me there.
你告诉他们什么了？
What'd you tell 'em?
全部 我什么也没做
Everything. I didn't do anything.
我告诉他们我拍的照片…
I told them about the pictures in the camera…
180航班 弗兰基和路易斯的事…
and Flight 180 and Frankie and Lewis…
还有我们为什么去找依安和埃琳
and why we went to see lan and Erin and…
他们信你吗？
Did they believe you?
是啊 你信我吗？
Yeah, right. Would you believe me?
不 他们看着我好像我疯了
No, they looked at me like I was crazy.
他们拖了我们10个小时
10 hours they had us in there.
我估计…
For all we know…
不管谁坐在埃琳后面 他们已经死了
whoever was sitting behind Erin is already dead.
接下去就是我们
And we're next.
现在
Now.
依安差点先死 但是因为我们的干预
lan almost died first, but we intervened.
死神跳过了依安 我们又夺回了控制权
So it skipped lan. That's… that's how we regain control.
如果有人从中干预…
If someone intercedes…
下一个人就会别跳过
the life that was supposed to be next is skipped.
对 等等
All right, wait, wait, wait.
那么 根据座位顺序…
So, going by the way we sat on the roller coaster…
下一个轮到我 然后是你
Well, I'm next… and then you.
我们能打破这个
We can beat this.
我们已经很接近了 不能放弃
We're so close. We can't give up.
我爸爸来了 他来接我回去
All right, my dad's here. He's gonna give me a ride back.
你确定我们不用呆在一起吗？
But are you sure we shouldn't stick together?
就分开几个小时
It's just for a couple of hours.
好吗？就几个小时
All right? A couple of hours.
你回去后 好好看看照片 看能不能找到更多线索…
Go back, look at the pictures, see if you can find any more clues…
我回去问所有我认识的人 看他们是否知道还有谁没有坐那节车
and I'll ask everybody I see if they know if anyone else got off the ride.
好吗？
OK?
还有什么要让我知道的吗？
Was there something I should know about going?
没了 只是…
No, it's just…
我每分每秒都会为你提心吊胆…
I'll just be freaking out every second…
希望你会没事
hoping you're OK.
为什么？
Why?
我是说 我们彼此都不欣赏对方
I mean, we don't even like each other.
呵呵
Heh.
过来
Come here.
好点吗？
OK?
好了 我带着手机
All right, I got my cell.
好
OK.
嘿 温
Hey, Wen?
我约了人一起参加纪念日庆典…
So we're meeting some guys at that centennial thing…
我真的需要我的…幸运手链
and I could really use my good-luck…bracelet.
嘿 我是茱丽 请留言
Hey, this is Julie. Leave a message.
马上给我回电话
Call me on my cell right away.
喂？
Hello?
记得吗 茱丽也上云霄飞车了
Do you remember Julie being on the roller coaster?
什么 你妹妹？不
What, your sister? No.
如果她上了 她会说的
No, she would've said something by now.
坐在依安和埃琳后面的人…
The person sitting behind lan and Erin…
带着相同款式的魔法手链…
was wearing the exact same charm bracelet…
祖母留给她的
our grandmother gave her.
安泊和帕丽很可能和她在一起…
Amber or Perry were probably with her…
所以接下去就是她们
so they're next.
我必须找到茱丽
I gotta find Julie.
她出去参加纪念日庆典了
She went to the tricentennial thing.
我就在这 做保安
Well, l…I'm here now, working security.
我来找她
I'll start looking for her.
- 我就来 - 温 等等
- I'm on my way. - Wen, wait.
听着 她们后面就轮到我们了
Look, after them, we're next.
万一我们也跟着出事…
So in case somethin' happens to 'em…
在见面之前…
before we meet up…
记得我们上次说好的吗？
remember that time we talked about?
何时看我们的照片？
When to look at our pictures?
现在是时候了
It's now.
太棒了 我的上面没有线索
Great. Mine has no clue.
就是我站在黑色背景前…
It's just me standing in front of a blank background…
和杰森一起 在游乐园
with Jason at the amusement park.
等等 麦金利
Wait. McKinley.
依安？他也在照片里？
lan? ls he in the picture?
不 没有 但这似乎是个线索
No, but it…it feels like a clue.
你的照片 我拍的时候…
And yours is the picture that I took…
对着你的脸打了闪光灯
when I flashed the camera in your face.
焦距不对 感光过度 好像…
It's all out of focus and overexposed, like…
好像焰火溅到我脸上？
Like a firework went off in my face?
有人
There is someone
走在你的身后
Walking behind you
看着我
Look at me
有人
There is someone
注视着你的脚步
Watching your footsteps
看着我
Look at me
有人
There is someone
那样深爱你
Who really loves you
英国人来了！英国人来了！
The British are coming! The British are coming!
- 哇哦 - 棒极了
- Whoo! - Yay!
乘胜追击
Get 'em while they're hot!
把那个给红衣军
Take it to those Redcoats!
起步 走
Column, advance!
风筝飞上了高天
The kite is aloft.
让我们期待着燃放焰火吧
Now, let us hope for some lightning.
去死吧 本·弗兰克林
Fuck you, Ben Franklin.
但要强调 滚开这 对吧？
But he kept insisting."Get over here " right?
真可怕
This is awesome dude!
呵呵
Heh heh.
哇哦 嘿！
Whoa. Hey!
来啊
Ha ha! Come on!
嘿 出去 把那掐了
Hey, get out of here with those, man! You're gonna set these off!
快点 伙计
Hurry, dude.
来啊 快点
Come on, man, let's go! Hurry up!
女士们先生们 为庆祝麦金利镇建镇300年…
Ladies and gentlemen, to celebrate McKinley's tricentennial…
焰火表演马上就要开始了
the fireworks extravaganza will begin shortly.
哦 上帝啊 茱丽
Oh, my God. Julie.
- 什么？- 看
- What? - Look.
那是卡利尔
There's Kahlil.
我们要不要？
Should we?
朋友 抱歉 你们不能呆在这儿
Hey, guys. I'm sorry, but you can't be here, OK?
看台在那边 你也是先生 请离开
The viewing site is over there. You too, sir. Come on.
他们不想让我们离开 对吧？
They're not gonna make us move are they?
我不相信他们！
I don't fucking believe them.
- 清场了 - 嗯嗯
- OK, we gotta clear out. - Mm-hm.
对不起
Excuse me.
- 小姐们 - 帅哥
- Ladies. - Boys.
近来怎样？
What's going on?
嘿 茱丽
Hey, Julie.
- 你们三个得跟我来 - 我们做什么了？
- You three need to come with me. - What did we do?
听着 是为了你们的安全 茱丽
Look, it's for your own safety, Julie, all right?
一离开这儿我就告诉你原因 好吗？
I'll tell you about it as soon as we get away from here, OK?
放开我！
Let go of me!
茱丽
Julie.
嘿
Hey whoa whoa whoa.
茱丽
Julie!
- 小可爱 - 哈
- Sweet. - Ha ha!
嗯！
Yeah!
点起来 点起来！
Light it! Light it! Go, go, go, man!
茱丽！
Julie!
哦！
Uh! Oh!
- 该死的 - 我们成保证人了
- Oh shit! - Dude we gotta bail!
茱丽 不 等等
Julie! No, wait, wait.
你很危险 听我解释
You're in danger, OK? I'm trying to explain something.
你听我解释吧
Let me explain this to you.
茱丽 小心！
Julie, look out!
- 啊哈！- 噢！
- Aah! - Unh!
啊哈！
Aah!
茱丽！
Julie!
噢！
Unh!
啊哈！噢！
Aah! Unh!
拦住它
Cut him off!
噢！
Unh!
啊哈！
Aah!
好了 好了
OK, OK.
退后 它很危险
Stay back! He's dangerous!
我牵住它了
I got him.
- 让我走 - 不 茱丽
- Just let me go. - No, Julie.
你必须告诉我 听着
You have to tell me, you have to listen.
告诉我那天在云霄飞车上 谁坐在你旁边
Tell me who was sitting next to you on the roller coaster!
哦 上帝 茱丽 你没事吧？
Oh, my God, Julie, are you all right?
听着 快告诉我…
Listen to me! You have to tell me…
在云霄飞车上坐在你旁边的是谁
who was sitting next to you on the roller coaster!
是谁？下一个就轮到她了！
Who? She's next!
嗯！
Aah!
凯文
Kevin.
哈！
Aah!
着火了
Fire!
凯文
Kevin.
你救了我
You saved my life.
多谢你了 麦金利
Thanks for that, McKinley.
- 闭嘴 麦金利 - 不！
- Shut up, McKinley! - No!
我们必须离开这里
We have to get out of here now.
怎么了？
What's the deal?
依安·麦金利 让我丧命的就是他
lan McKinley. He causes my death.
在照片里 我穿了件麦金利校服
ln my picture I was wearing the McKinley grad night shirt.
- 他就是那个线索 - 什么？
- He's the clue. - What?
那里有个救援帐篷 那里很安全
There's a first aid tent, there should be security.
滚开 麦金利
Get the fuck outta here, McKinley!
嘿 我是来庆贺建镇300周年纪念的
Hey, I'm just celebrating our town's tricentennial.
你跟着我来的
You followed me!
你有妄想症吧
Oh! You are paranoid.
不过 刚才的事我看到了
But, hey, I saw what happened.
你是下一个对不对？你是最后一个人 不是吗？
You're next, right? You're the end of it, aren't you?
老兄 我好像也有妄想症了
Man, I would be paranoid, too.
你根本没相信过我
You didn't even believe me!
是啊 眼见为实嘛
Yeah, well, seeing is believing.
那你就必须离我远点
Then you have to stay away from me!
「必须」 太过分了
"Have to"? Wow, that's extreme.
不 不可能
Oh, no way.
是我让你死的？
Do I cause your death?
就像你导致了埃琳的死？
Just like you caused Erin's?
怎么了 怎么了？
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what? What?
你看到幻觉了吗 里面有我吗？
You have a vision? Was I in it?
照片里有我吗？
Was I in a picture?
告诉我怎么做
Just tell me how to start it off!
让我来结束这一切
Let's get this over with!
你别靠近我 我就得救了
You'll save me if you just stay away!
这样一切就都结束了
Then it'll all be over!
我管你干什么？反正我已经被跳过了
What do I care? lt skipped me.
对于我来说 已经结束了 我不会死
For me, it is over. I'm not dying.
我不会死
I'm not dying!
哈哈哈！
Ha ha ha!
看见没有？
You see?
我不会死！
I'm not gonna die!
该死的是你 温迪 你死定了
It's you, Wendy! You're dead!
（5个月后）
你好！
Hi!
谢谢
Thank you.
等等 那个超好的咖喱店怎么样？
Wait, what about that great curry place?
我们不是应该在布斯下车吗？
Don't we get off at Booth?
你是说格帕斯 应该在奥斯沃下车
Oh, you mean Gupta's. You get off at Oswald.
哦 对
Oh, that's right.
如果感恩节不能回家的话…
You know, if I can't be home for Thanksgiving…
我必须自己弄点传统食物吃 让自己感觉回家
I need some semblance of a traditional dinner.
火鸡 酱 派
Turkey, stuffing, pie.
就一次感恩节不吃火鸡…
If you don't have turkey for one Thanksgiving…
会难受死吗？
is that really gonna kill you?
有人
There is someone
走在你身后
Walking behind you
转过身
Turn around
看着我
Look at me
有人
There is someone
注视着你的脚步
Watching your footsteps
转过身
Turn around
有人
There is someone
真的需要你
Who really needs you
给你我的真心
Here's my heart
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
列车即将到达布斯街
This is Booth Street.
下一站 终点站 奥斯沃
Next stop is Oswald. End of the line.
下一站是终点站
The next stop is the end of the line.
温迪！这站停了还有一站才下
Wendy! Next stop after this.
- 我们走过去吧 - 外面冻死了
- Let's just walk. - It's freezing out.
是啊 但空气好
Yeah, but the air'll feel good.
我需要点空气
I could use some air.
是啊
Yeah!
哈哈 是啊 伙计
Ha ha ha! Yeah, man!
好了 回见
All right, man. See ya.
我们走 黑熊！
Let's go, Bruins!
黑熊！
Bruins, yeah!
嘿 伙计 静点
Hey man peace out!
- 下吧 - 对不起
- Come on. - Excuse me.
- 看着点 - 嘿 黑熊
- Watch out! - Hey, Bruins!
你错过开头了 你看了吗？
You missed the beginning. Did you see that?
就是那样
This is it!
对不起 借过一下
Yo, comin' through. Excuse me.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
真不敢相信 过来
I can't believe this. Here.
没关系 我们走 我们走
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
我以为你们今晚前到不了
I thought you weren't coming tilI tonight.
爸爸的车到哪儿都能抛锚…
Well, Dad's car just, like, dies out of nowhere…
过节了连个修车的地方都找不到…
and he couldn't get it fixed anywhere on a holiday…
与其坐着等几个小时…
so instead of sitting around for a few hours…
不如搭头班车
I lucked out and caught an early train.
我希望我没有打乱你的计划吧
I hope I'm not messing you up or…
不 没有 只是…
No, no, it's just, um…
我觉得我感觉到你马上就会来
I think I had a sense that you were coming now.
我感到…
I was just…
我觉得那天晚上的感觉又来了
I was feeling like I did that night.
不 都结束了
No. No, it's over.
你 我 凯文 都逃过了
You, me, Kevin went over a thousand scenarios.
依安本来会杀了你…
lan was gonna cause your death…
但是你阻止了他 所以我们都被跳过了
you intervened, and it skipped us.
听着 我一点也不担心
Look, I'm not worried.
我碰到过凯文 他也一点不担心
I ran into Kevin at home. He's not worried.
如果我是你…
And, if I were you…
在我和凯文出事之前…
until something happens to me and then Kevin…
根本就没什么好担心的
you've got nothing to worry about.
你说得对
You're right.
呃
Uhh.
嘿 来见见我的室友和朋友
Hey, I…I want you to meet my roommate and my friend, OK?
好啊
Yeah.
这是茱丽 我的…
Hey, guys. This is Julie, my…
你怎么在这？
What are you doing here?
温迪！茱丽！
Wendy! Julie!
真是太巧了！
What are the chances?
你上这班车多久了？
How long have you been on this train?
从我家那边上车的
Uh, since home.
我一直在研究这个游戏
I was headin' up to check out the game.
本来应该看到你的
I was gonna look you up afterwards.
你没事吧？
You OK?
出什么问题了吗？
ls something wrong?
啊哈！
Aah!
- 茱丽 蹲下 - 啊哈！
- Julie, stay down! - Aah!
茱丽！
Julie!
啊哈！
Aah!
- 凯文！- 呃！
- Kevin! - Unh!
啊 啊 啊
Aaaaaah!
哦 上帝啊
Oh, God!
啊哈！
Aah!
啊哈！噢！
Aah! Unh!
不！
No!
本来应该看到你的 但是…
I was gonna look you up afterwards, but…
你没事吧？
You OK?
出什么问题了吗？
ls somethin' wrong?
这辆车…
The train…
哦 见鬼 不会吧
Oh, shit. Not again.
我们必须下车！
We gotta get out!
不管用了 有人吗 停车！
It's not working. Somebody stop the train!